(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Hello?
is...
...anybody...
...there?
it's so...
...dark...
No one gets it...
No one...
...understands.
I feel...
I feel... hunger...
I feel... cold...
please...
Is...
...anybody...
...there?
"(hello)"
シャンティ 作詞・作曲: wotaku
Shanti Lyrics/Composition: wotaku
やあ、売られた喧嘩はその兄ちゃん
Hey there, you're the one who started that fight,
なんか辛いことがあったんか
did something painful happen to you?
降りておいでよ話してくんない
Come on down and talk to me,
力になるぜ
I'll give you a hand.
一体どんなことがあった
Just what exactly happened?
それ言ってみ話して兄弟
Tell me about it, talk to me, brother.
これをやっから元気出しな
Have one of these and cheer up,
金なら払ってこんでいいさ
you don't even need to pay me.
シャンティ シャンティ シャンティ シャンティ ハッピーキャンディ
Shanti Shanti Shanti Shanti Happy Candy
ハッピー ハッピー ハッピーキャンディ メニーメニーマネー
Happy Happy Happy Candy Many Many Money
眠れない夜のチャイナタウン
In this sleepless Chinatown night,
嘘も全てがモノ語り
even lies are all part of the story.
老若男女は御客さん
Men and women of all ages are our customers,
代わってお得でイェーイ
a great deal in exchange, yay!
今夜も来たのかい
Did you come again tonight?
お気に召したかい
Did you find it to your liking?
代金はこれくらい
The price is about this much.
え？
Eh?
払えないのかい
You can't pay?
ならばしょうがない
Well then, it can't be helped.
君にぴったりの仕事があるから
I have a job that's perfect for you,
こっちについてきな
so come along with me.
Come along with me.
こっちに付いてきな
Come with me.
焼かれた酒場が 剥がれたオンナ
A burnt-down bar, a woman stripped of her mask.
しゃがれた看板 掲げたオーナー
A hoarse sign, a proud owner.
誰彼構わず 刺さるよ容赦
Without regard for anyone, it pierces without mercy.
はなからアイツの 思惑通り
Right from the start, just as they intended.
着狂ってればサンプル中
If you're crazy about clothes, you're just another sample.
チールとマインド特
Chilling and a specialized mind.
上昇ドリーミング 咲かせて果てなし
Rising dreams, blooming without end.
四の五の言わず 畳めよ
Stop making excuses and get to work.
黙れ座れ 黙れ座れや
Shut up and sit down. Shut up and sit down.
舐めろ舐めろ 舐めろ舐めろや
Lick it, lick it. Lick it, lick it.
縛れ縛れ 縛れ縛れや
Tie it up, tie it up. Tie it up, tie it up.
バラせバラせ バラせバラせや
Take it apart, take it apart.
今宵はオーダール お気に召すかい
Will the order tonight please you?
代償はこれくらい
The price is about this much.
生きてればオキャク
If you're alive, you're a customer.
死んでればショザイ
If you're dead, you're material.
損得抜きなく これこそビジネス
Regardless of profit or loss, this is business.
どっちを向いてんだ
Which way are you facing?
いや どっちを向いてんだ
Hey, which way are you facing?
どっちを向いてんだ
Which way are you facing?
やぁ 乱れてるその情緒
Oh, those disordered emotions.
俺とゆっくり話してくんね
Why don't you have a nice long talk with me?
Chuunibyou...
...those with grandiose delusions,
those desperate to stand out,
and who have convinced themselves
that they have hidden knowledge or secret powers.
I...
...feel it.
it's in my veins.
my...
...head.
my head...
...keeps pounding...
something is calling me
“who are you?”
if the darkness beckons
then who's to stop me
空想メソロギヰ
Fantasy Mythology
Consentes Dii Juno Jupiter
Minerva Apollo Mars Ceres
Mercurius Diana Bacchus
Vulcanus Pluto Vesta Venus
まどろみの星標(しる)して
Aiming for the slumbering star-marker
瞼に揺蕩う
Swaying behind my eyelids
無双の神は優雅に微笑み
The peerless god smiles elegantly
死を贈る
And bestows death
軸を統べる因果の鎖
The chains of causality that govern space-time
まき散らす
Scattering them about
神の与えし
Bestowed by God
ケイショウ プログラム
Program of succession
サバイバル ゲーム
A survival game
螺旋のように
Like a spiral
さぁ 哀 望(あい) サバイバル 重なり合う
Now, sorrow and desire, survival, overlapping
さぁ 哀 望(あい) サバイバル 詩を交わして
Now, sorrow and desire, survival, exchanging poems
消滅の遊戯に
In the game of extinction
焦がれる奇跡を歌う
Singing of the miracle I yearn for
サバイバル ゲーム
Survival game
螺旋のように
Like a spiral
Consentes Dii Juno Jupiter
Minerva Apollo Mars Ceres
Mercurius Diana Bacchus
Vulcanus Pluto Vesta Venus
泡沫の未来
A transient future
書き換えるように
As if to rewrite it
葛藤を繋ぐ因縁の
The gears of fate that link conflicts
歯車が鳴り渡る
Ring out loudly
時間は歪み因果の
Time distorts, and the discipline
規律は崩れ去る
Of causality crumbles away
神の与えし
Bestowed by God
ケイショウ プログラム
Program of succession
サバイバル ゲーム
A survival game
さあ Eins, Zwei, Drei 繋なり合う
Now, eins, zwei, drei, we're intertwining.
さあ Eins, Zwei, Drei 死を振り切って
Now, eins, zwei, drei, shaking off death...
消滅の指に
...on the finger of extinction...
荒削りに挑む Survival Game
...challenging this unrefined survival game.
Eraser Game
無限のように
Just like infinity.
さあ Eins, Zwei, Drei 繋なり合う
Now, eins, zwei, drei, we're intertwining.
さあ Eins, Zwei, Drei 死を交わして
Now, eins, zwei, drei, dodging death...
Eins, Zwei, Drei 繋なり合う
Eins, zwei, drei, we're intertwining.
さあ Eins, Zwei, Drei 死を振り切って
Now, eins, zwei, drei, shaking off death...
消滅の指に
...on the finger of extinction...
荒削りな奇跡を歌う Survival Game
...singing of unrefined miracles in this survival game.
螺旋のように
Just like a spiral.
ハイエナの冒険譚
A hyena's adventure tale...
焦がれる生死 夜を研ぐ
...longing for life or death, sharpening the night.
最果てにある箱にまで終わりのない Survival Game
A survival game without end, even to the box at the world's edge.
信じてた
I believed.
くだらない依存関係だ
It's a worthless codependency.
ディープカバー / 作詞：DECO*27 作曲：Rockwell
Deep Cover / Lyrics: DECO*27 Composition: Rockwell
はしたない温もりの凝る
Coagulating with vulgar warmth.
馬鹿じゃん 馬鹿じゃんね
You're an idiot, aren't you?
また生きてさ 生きてさ 際ね
Living again, living, it's the limit.
変わらない 巡るクレーンゲーム
Unchanging, a revolving crane game.
救えない 恵みのスリラー
An unsavable thriller of blessings.
馬鹿じゃん 馬鹿じゃんね
You're an idiot, aren't you?
また愛してさ 愛してさ きついね
Loving again, loving, it's tough.
どれかがいらないの
I don't need one of them.
許さないが走ったから
Because unforgiveness has broken out...
貴方の牙になったよ
...I've become your fangs.
待望のヒーロー選んだよ
I chose the long-awaited hero.
回答を刻み込んだよ
I carved the answer into me.
やめてなんて何で 何でなの?
"Stop," you say? Why, why is that?
止まらないでよ
Don't stop.
裁きを下す大義名分が
I want the moral justification...
欲しい 欲しいの
...to pass judgment. I want it.
次の夢をくれよ
Give me the next dream.
隠したい 破りたい 競反撥
Wanting to hide, wanting to break, competing rebellion.
留めない 踏み込まない 信仰心
Not staying, not stepping in, religious devotion.
馬鹿じゃん 馬鹿じゃんね
You're an idiot, aren't you?
待ち覚えてない 覚えてない 鈍いね
Not remembering waiting, not remembering, how dull.
使い難い 記憶の監獄で
In the hard-to-use prison of memory...
揺れてたい 笑っちゃう正義
...I want to sway, laughing at justice.
馬鹿じゃん 馬鹿じゃんね
You're an idiot, aren't you?
ドアをノックして置くか
Shall I leave after knocking on the door?
だから私の理由になったよ
So, it became my reason.
許さないだけ選んだよ
I chose only not to forgive.
同情は閉まっていてよ
Keep your sympathy to yourself.
悪を悪と憎んでよ
Hate evil as evil.
止まらないでよ
Don't stop.
裁きを下す大義名分が
I want the moral justification...
欲しい 欲しいの
...to pass judgment. I want it.
次の夢をくれよ
Give me the next dream.
下る
Under
溶かしたい 求めてた正義
Wanting to melt the justice I sought.
潰したい 汚れた未来を
Wanting to crush the tainted future.
馬鹿じゃん 馬鹿じゃんね
You're an idiot, aren't you?
頼ってよ ほら
Lean on me, see.
貴方の牙になったよ
I've become your fangs.
待望のヒーロー選んだよ
I chose the long-awaited hero.
回答を刻み込んだよ
I carved the answer into me.
やめてなんて何で 何でなの?
"Stop," you say? Why, why is that?
止まらないでよ
Don't stop.
裁きを下す大義名分が
I want the moral justification...
欲しい 欲しいの
...to pass judgment. I want it.
次の夢をくれよ
Give me the next dream.
欲しい 欲しいの
I want it, I want it.
次の夢をくれよ
Give me the next dream.
くだらない 「001 寄生虫」
Worthless: "001 Parasite"
はしたない 「002 淫乱嬢」
Vulgar: "002 Nympho"
変わらない 「004 偽女王」
Unchanging: "004 Pseudo-Queen"
救えない 「005 解剖兵」
Unsavable: "005 Anatomy Soldier"
隠したい 「007 虚言人」
Wanting to hide: "007 Liar"
使い難い 「011 牢監視」
Hard to use: "011 Jailer"
馬鹿じゃん 馬鹿じゃんね
You're an idiot, aren't you?
ほらごっちさ ごっちさ 際ね
See, this way, this way, it's the limit.
...I feel myself falling...
...into complete deafening darkness.
A blanket of monochrome solitude...
there is no one.
Alone.
you're not alone
I'm alone
I'm all alone
僕が...
I am...
...僕がついてる
...I am with you.
she is coming...
The time has come
DARK ARIA
To pack away all the joys
You don't want to hear my apology
Get it off my chest, I would do my best
I know what you feel
Similarities we possess
Never will I pass the test
The scene is fading
Can my soul be put to rest?
Death is gonna come for me
Be the change I couldn't be
Can you find a life that's like fairy tales
Far from this tragedy?
Said you had to wait for me
Feels like an eternity
Please forgive me for my sins
Angels' wings lifting and setting me free
Death is gonna come for me
Be the change I couldn't be
Can you find a life that's like fairy tales
Far from this tragedy?
Said you had to wait for me
Feels like an eternity
Please forgive me for my sins
Angels' wings lifting and setting me free
The question of my love
Slipping right through
The cracks
And crumbling to dust
The question of my love
Slipping right through
The cracks
And crumbling to dust
synchronicity
この温もりは
Where is this warmth
どこへ行くの
heading to?
明日になれば
By tomorrow,
消えてしまうの
will it vanish?
胸の鼓動
If we align
合わせたならば
our heartbeats,
同じ深みへ
can we descend
降りてゆけるの
to the same depths?
いつも
Always,
always,
側にいるよ
I'm by your side.
どんな 遠く
No matter how far
君の心が迷っても
your heart wanders.
暗闇の中に二人で漂いながら
As the two of us drift in the darkness,
無邪気な小鳥のように翼を寄せていた
we drew our wings close like innocent birds.
寂しい時には笑顔に隠れる君は
When you're lonely, hiding behind a smile,
解けない...
an unsolvable...
凍りの刃
An icy blade
この胸をさらして
Baring my chest
抱きしめる
I'll embrace you
ずっと
Forever
君は一人で
You're all alone
どこへ行くの？
Where are you going?
振り返るのが
Is it only because
怖いだけなの？
You're afraid to look back?
胸の形も
The shape of your heart
悲しい色も
The color of your sadness
本当はきっと
In truth, I'm sure
よく似てるのに
They look so much alike
いつかきっと
One day, surely
帰る場所を
Our place to return to
二人同じ
We both search with
儚さで見つめている
The same fleeting gaze
この闇の中で
In the midst of this darkness
どんなに離れていても
No matter how far apart we are
心は何より強い
The heart is bound by
絆で呼び合って
A bond stronger than anything
淋しい時君は
When you're lonely
笑っていてもわかるよ
I can tell even if you're smiling
冷たい指を涙で
I want to warm your cold fingers
暖めてあげたい
With my tears
側にいる
I'm by your side
I can see you in my mind
You and me
I can feel you in my mind
Be with me and so
I can see you in my mind
You and me
I can feel you in my mind
Be with me
暗闇の中に
While drifting through
二人で漂いながら
The pitch-black darkness
無邪気な小鳥のように
Like innocent little birds
翼を寄せていた
Drawing our wings together
淋しい時君は
When you're lonely
笑顔に隠れる君は
And hiding behind a smile
解けない凍りの刃
Like an unbreakable icy blade
この胸をさらして
Baring my chest
抱きしめる
I'll embrace you
側にいる
I'm by your side
ずっと...
Forever...
Have you ever looked through rose colored glasses?
A touch of red in our black and grey world...
...one of pain and misery...
DROWNING
SUFFOCATING
LOATHING
DESPAIR
僕らの世界を色眼鏡で見たことある？
Have you ever gazed at our world through rose colored glasses?
見てごらんよ きっと気づくでしょう
You should give it a try... For I'm sure you too will realize
こんなに素敵な色があったなんて
Has there ever been a more beautiful color?
赤く染めよう
Drown everything in Red.
調和 oto ~with reflection~
作詞・作曲：KOKIA
Chouwa oto ~with reflection~
Lyrics & Composition: KOKIA
静けさの中
In the silence
一つ落ちただけ
Just one fell
広がる波紋に
To the spreading ripples
波打つ命の底
Bottom of the waving life
ざわついた私の心の森を揺さぶる
Shaking the forest of my noisy heart
木枯らしよ
Oh, winter wind
今日を堪えて切れるものなら
If I can endure today and cut through it
そのままの私でいさせて
Let me be as I am
誰もがこの森で
Everyone in this forest
静かな声を聞いて
Listen to the quiet voice
雑音に涙した
Cried at the noise
ルレクデシエカ
Rurekudeshiyeka
ボキトナカヤハタ
Bokitonakayahata
ボニココトオシイタバ
Bonikokotooshiitaba
カイツバザデカアスシテ
Kaitsubazadekaasushite
シソクナマエタ
Shisokunamaeta
トクメシニリモホホコ
Tokumeshinirimomohohoko
ルレクデシエカ
Rurekudeshiyeka
ボキトナカヤハタ
Bokitonakayahata
ボニココトオシイタバ
Bonikokotooshiitaba
カイツバザデカアスシテ
Kaitsubazadekaasushite
シソクナマエタ
Shisokunamaeta
トクメシニリモホホコ
Tokumeshinirimomohohoko
フレナブ フレナブ フレナブ オト
Furenabu Furenabu Furenabu Oto
ニミョモオト デンシデンシデンシ
Nimyomooto Denshidenshidenshi
フレナブ フレナブ フレナブ オト
Furenabu Furenabu Furenabu Oto
ニミョモオト オロモオロモオロモ
Nimyomooto Oromooromooromo
ルレクデシエカ
Rurekudeshiyeka
ボキトナカヤハタ
Bokitonakayahata
ボニココトオシイタバ
Bonikokotooshiitaba
カイツバザデカアスシテ
Kaitsubazadekaasushite
シソクナマエタ
Shisokunamaeta
トクメシニリモホホコ
Tokumeshinirimomohohoko
ルレクデシエカ
Rurekudeshiyeka
ボキトナカヤハタ
Bokitonakayahata
ボニココトオシイタバ
Bonikokotooshiitaba
カイツバザデカアスシテ
Kaitsubazadekaasushite
ルレクデシエカ
Rurekudeshiyeka
ボキトナカヤハタ
Bokitonakayahata
ボニココトオシイタバ
Bonikokotooshiitaba
カイツバザデカアスシテ
Kaitsubazadekaasushite
シソクナマエタ
Shisokunamaeta
トクメシニリモホホコ
Tokumeshinirimomohohoko
ルレクデシエカ
Rurekudeshiyeka
ボキトナカヤハタ
Bokitonakayahata
ボニココトオシイタバ
Bonikokotooshiitaba
カイツバザデカアスシテ
Kaitsubazadekaasushite
シソクナマエタ
Shisokunamaeta
トクメシニリモホホコ
Tokumeshinirimomohohoko
ルレクデシエカ
Rurekudeshiyeka
ボキトナカヤハタ
Bokitonakayahata
ボニココトオシイタバ
Bonikokotooshiitaba
カイツバザデカアスシテ
Kaitsubazadekaasushite
シソクナマエタ
Shisokunamaeta
トクメシニリモホホコ
Tokumeshinirimomohohoko
三十路岬
作詞：畑亜貴 作曲：神前暁
Misoji Misaki
Lyrics: Aki Hata Composition: Satoru Kousaki
三十路岬
Misoji Misaki (Misoji Cape)
作詞：畑亜貴 作曲：神前暁
Lyrics: Aki Hata / Composition: Satoru Kosaki
一人語りしてもいいですか
Is it okay if I talk to myself?
カモメにそっとつぶやいた
I softly whispered to the seagulls
女一途な真心乗せて
Carrying a woman's devoted sincerity
北の海風凍てついた
The northern sea breeze froze
はぐれ恋散る
A stray love scatters
怨み節さえ
Even the grudges
遠いあんたにゃ届かない
Won't reach you, who are far away
佇んで泣き濡れて
Standing still, wet with tears
三十路岬
Misoji Cape
二人だけど宿で泣き崩れ
The two of us together, yet I broke down in tears at the inn
愛した夜を悔やんでも
Even if I regret the nights I loved you
男勝手な約束ばかり
Only selfish promises from a man
何もかなわず終わります
Everything ends without coming true
波のしぶきにこの身投げたら
If I threw myself into the sea spray
怨み節さえ
Even the grudges
遠いあんたに愛想尽きて
Fed up with you, who are far away
恋しさに捧げたい
I want to offer to my love
三十路魂
Misoji Soul
三つ巴の愛としりもせず
Not even knowing it was a three-way love
愛した罪は消えないの
The sin of having loved will not disappear
誰を選んで決められないと
Saying you can't choose who to be with
別れ上手な人でした
You were someone good at saying goodbye
はぐれ恋散る
A stray love scatters
怨み節さえ
Even the grudges
熱い思い出枯れ果てた
Hot memories have completely dried up
恋しくて憎いのよ
I miss you and I hate you
三十路岬
Misoji Cape
中二病って何だ...
What is... chuunibyou?
ずっと探してた答えは一体何なんだ。
What is the answer I've been searching for this whole time?
今までたどり着いた答えが納得できぬ。
I cannot accept the path I've walked on till now...
ならば、
If that's the case...
自分で作るさ！
then I'll make my own.
本当の中二病は...
The true meaning of chuunibyou...
そう...
that's right...
すべては...
everything is about...
魂だ!!!!!!!!!
THE SOUL!
めざめよ!!!
AWAKEN!!!
MY SOUL!!
遥か彼方
作詞・作曲 後藤正文
Haruka Kanata
Lyrics/Composition: Masafumi Gotou
踏み込むさアクセル
Step on the accelerator
駆け引きは無いさ そうだよ
There's no strategy, that's right
夜を抜ける
Tear through the night
ねじ込むさ最後に
Force it through at the end
差し引きゼロさ そうだよ
It all balances out to zero, that's right
日々を削る
Shaving away the days
心をそっと
Gently, your heart...
開いてギュッと
...open it up and hold tight
引き寄せたら
If you pull it close
届くよきっと
It will surely reach
伝うよもっと さぁ
It will convey even more, come on
生き急いで
Live for the moment
絞り取って
Squeeze out every drop
縺れる足だけど前よりずっと遠くへ
My legs are stumbling, but I'll go much further than before
奪い取って
Take it back
掴み取って
Grasp it tight
君じゃないなら意味は無いのさ だからもっと思っともっと 遙か彼方
If it's not you, there's no meaning, so further, further, further beyond
踏み込むさアクセル
Step on the accelerator
駆け引きは無いさ そうだよ
There's no strategy, that's right
夜を抜ける
Tear through the night
ねじ込むさ最後に
Force it through at the end
差し引きゼロさ そうだよ
It all balances out to zero, that's right
日々を削る
Shaving away the days
心をそっと
Gently, your heart...
開いてギュッと
...open it up and hold tight
引き寄せたら
If you pull it close
届くよきっと
It will surely reach
伝うよもっと さぁ
It will convey even more, come on
生き急いで
Live for the moment
絞り取って
Squeeze out every drop
縺れる足だけど前よりずっと遠くへ
My legs are stumbling, but I'll go much further than before
奪い取って
Take it back
掴み取って
Grasp it tight
君じゃないなら意味は無いのさ だからもっと思っともっと 遙か彼方
If it's not you, there's no meaning, so further, further, further beyond
偽ることに慣れた君の世界を
Your world that's grown accustomed to deception
塗り潰すのさ白く
Paint it over in pure white
足りねえ！
Not enough!
全然足りねえ！
Not enough at all!
I NEED MORE SOUL!
JUDGEMENT -審判- (Full Spec Edition)
作詞：瀬井亮介 作曲：Hyd Lunch
Lyrics: Ryosuke Seto Composition: Hyd Lunch
レールからはずれた 不良品の野良犬さ
Just a stray dog, a reject off the rails
(GO! GO! GO!)
だけど簡単には テールは振らないぜ
But I won't wag my tail so easily
(A-HA! OK! I NEED NISKY!)
・・・レールからはずれた 不良品の野良犬さ だけど簡単には 手綱は振らせないぜ
...A stray dog of a defective product off the rails, but I won't let you hold the reins so easily.
大人－イエスマンに－成りそびれた
I failed to become an adult—a "yes-man".
Whoa, we are bad boys
若者―ワルに―残された「No」という名のJustice
Justice called "No" left to the youth—the delinquents.
Now, Breakin' the law Breakin' the world 壊せ
Now, Breakin' the law Breakin' the world, break it!
Breakin' the world 壊せ 切り裂けTenderness
Breakin' the world, break it! Slice it up, tenderness.
Now, Breakin' the rule 六法全書じゃ縛れない
Now, Breakin' the rule, you can't bind me with the Statute Books.
反乱分子さ
I'm a rebel.
振り上げた 握り拳が 俺たちのJUDGEMENT
Our raised fists are our JUDGEMENT.
愛さえも知らない 不良品の野良犬さ
A stray dog of a defective product that doesn't even know love.
だけど地位や金じゃ 餌付けはできないぜ
But you can't tame me with status or money.
・・・傷ついて 傷ついて 全て失っちまっても
...Even if I get hurt, get hurt, and lose everything.
染まっちゃならねえ それこそがJUSTICE・・・
I must not be tainted, that is exactly what JUSTICE is...
JUSTICE!
Now, Breakin' the law Breakin' the world 壊せ
Now, Breakin' the law Breakin' the world, break it!
Breakin' the world 壊せ 切り裂けTenderness
Breakin' the world, break it! Slice it up, tenderness.
Now, Breakin' the rule お偉いさんにゃ従わない
Now, Breakin' the rule, I won't obey the big shots.
反乱分子さ
I'm a rebel.
振り上げろ 握り拳を
Raise your fists.
俺たちは・・・ そうさ俺たちが
We are... That's right, we are
JUDGEMENT・・・
JUDGEMENT...
チート ギフテッド 俺様がボン 禁忌 禁忌 呆気なく昇天
Cheat, gifted, I'm the one who's born, taboo, taboo, easily astounding
反則 異端 異様なもんではないです 弁解 それ聞いてないって
Foul play, heresy, it's nothing unusual, excuse? I didn't hear that
Aye, ライバル 口を揃えて Wow, ライバル 口を揃えて
Aye, rivals, all exterminated, wow, rivals, all exterminated
バグで マグで 認めたぜって マジで これを待て 全部ナマ身で
By a bug, by luck, I've admitted it, seriously, wait for this, all in the flesh
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born
強く弾き切る前に 相手の方がバテてで暗いし I got a good hurdle very happy
Before I can strongly repel them, the opponent is already exhausted, I got a good hurdle very happy
Bling, Bang, Bang
お前の期待より愛せ 俺バットにできない ことばかり 抱けるベリーハッピー
Love me more than your expectations, I can't do things easily, but I'm very happy
呆れてる 呆れてる 周り脱ぐまで 全部家族 友達 もう反則的だ チームに俺に任せろバイビー
Shocked, shocked, until the surroundings are stripped, all family and friends, it's illegal, leave it to the team and me, bye-bye
鏡よ鏡 答えちゃって Who's the best? I'm the best! Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
Mirror, mirror on the wall, answer me, who's the best? I'm the best! Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
生身のまま行けるところまで To the next, to the 1番上
As I am, as far as I can go, to the next, to the top
Bling-Bang-Bang-Born... To the next, to the 1番上
Bling-Bang-Bang-Born... To the next, to the top
Ey-day 俺のままでいるだけで超フレックス Ey-day 誰も口を挟めない
Ey-day, just being myself is a super flex, ey-day, nobody can interrupt
誰も口は挟めない
No one can interfere
Don't test
隠れる気もない　全開も無い　言うてBling-Bling
No intent to hide, no limit, I say "Bling-Bling"
この存在自体が文化財の脳みそBling-Bling
This existence itself is a cultural asset, brains going "Bling-Bling"
極彩色ばかり目眩まない愛車Bling-Bling
Rich colors everywhere, never dazzled, devotion going "Bling-Bling"
全知全能かく地リラックス一遍このベロがBling-Bling
Omniscient, relaxed everywhere, this tongue going "Bling-Bling"
パレットなら満タン　関西訛り生身の言霊
Magazines are full, Kansai accent, living power of words
音楽も処理の女神今宵様々バンバン
Even music is a processing goddess, various things tonight, Bang-Bang
漫画みたいなカルトまんまり張り合いとなってしまってる漫画
A cult-like manga, it's become a manga where we're fully competing
圧倒的力　これであってもどき力
Overwhelming power, even with this, it's just a mock power
この下駄を履いていないこのツルに傷もついていない
Not wearing these clogs, not a scratch on this vine
繰り返しをかわして誰かがついてゆく目覚め芝居
Dodging the repetitions, someone follows the awakening performance
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born
俺のままでBling-Bang-Bang-Born
As I am, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born
鏡よ鏡、答えちゃって
Mirror, mirror, please answer
Who the best? I'm the best! Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
生身のまま行けるどこまで
How far can I go in the flesh?
To the next, to the 1番上
To the next, to the very top
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born
To the next, to the 1番上
To the next, to the very top
Ey day 俺のままにいるだけで超フレックス
Ey day, just by being myself, I'm super flex
Ey day 誰も口は挟めない Don't test
Ey day, no one can interfere, Don't test
Ey day 俺のままにいるだけで超フレックス
Ey day, just by being myself, I'm super flex
Ey day 誰も口は挟ませない Don't test
Ey day, I won't let anyone interfere, Don't test
Los! Los! Los!
Feuer! Sperrfeuer! Feuer! Los!
Fire! Barrage! Fire! Go!
Achtung! Deckung! Hinlegen! Halt!
Attention! Cover! Lie down! Stop!
戦場へ　前線へ　そして死の淵まで
To the battlefield, to the front lines, and to the brink of death
命捨てた　その覚悟を示せ
Show the resolve of having thrown away your life
Feuer! Sperrfeuer! Feuer! Los!
Fire! Barrage! Fire! Go!
聞こえるなら　あの咆哮(せい)が
If you can hear that roar
テイクオフする　魂(うち)の声だ
It's the voice of the soul taking off
踏み潰せ
Crush it underfoot
諸君、我々の任務は何だ？
Gentlemen, what is our mission?
殲滅だ！　一機残らずの殲滅だ！
Annihilation! Annihilation without leaving a single one!
為すべきことはただ一つ
There is only one thing to do
地獄を作れ！
Create hell!
鉄と火の雨に　打たれに行く合唱(こえ)
The chorus of voices going to be pelted by the rain of iron and fire
笑止千万！
Utterly ridiculous!
帝国の為だ！
It's for the Empire!
戦場へ　前線へ　そして死の淵まで
To the battlefield, to the front lines, and to the brink of death
命捨てた　覚悟を示せよ
Show the resolve of having thrown away your life
忠誠を　順従を　そしてその魂を
Loyalty, obedience, and that soul
すべて捧げ　勝鬨を上げよう
Offer everything and raise a victory cry
さあ此処に　築いてみせろ
Now, try and build it here
天に届く　死体の山を！
A mountain of corpses that reaches the heavens!
Feuer! Sperrfeuer! Feuer! Los!
Fire! Barrage! Fire! Go!
Achtung! Deckung! Hinlegen! Halt!
Attention! Cover! Lie down! Stop!
どこに恐怖が　あるというもんだ
Where do you say there is fear?
血飛沫(みち)抜くが　花火のようだ
Gushing blood is like fireworks
撒き散らせ
Scatter it
千の傷跡　忘れちゃいないさ
I haven't forgotten the thousand scars
焔の熱も　こぼれた情も
The heat of the flames, and the spilled emotions
断末魔最後(あと)の　呻きも見事(ひとみ)も
The last groans of death, and the moments
嗚呼それこそを　求めるのだ！
Ah, that is exactly what I seek!
慈悲(はね)も平和(へい)も　まして和解(わ)なんて
Mercy, peace, let alone reconciliation
牙を捨てた　飼い犬の症状(さが)を
The nature of a domestic dog that has lost its fangs
絶望と怒りを　かき混ぜ狂喜の沙汰は
Mixing despair and anger, the state of madness
地獄よりも　楽園のようだ
Is more like paradise than hell
その四肢は　踊るために
Those limbs are for dancing
踊り狂う　ためにあるのだ
They exist to dance madly
人間に価値など無い。価値なき者同士の争いに、命の徒花を咲かせてみせろ！
Humanity has no value. In the conflict between worthless beings, let the non-fruiting flowers of life bloom!
怯えも躊躇(ちゅう)も　狂った奴がつくってる
Fear and hesitation are created by the insane
まさにファルス　不条理(ふじょ)ばかりの
It's truly a farce, full of absurdity
起承転結！
Introduction, development, twist, and conclusion!
戦場へ　前線へ　そして死の淵まで
To the battlefield, to the front lines, and to the brink of death
命捨てた　覚悟を示せよ
Show the resolve of having thrown away your life
忠誠を　順従を　そして其の魂を
Loyalty, obedience, and that soul
すべて捧げ　勝鬨を上げよう
Offer everything and raise a victory cry
さあ此処に　築いてみせろ
Now, try and build it here
天に届く　死体の山に
On the mountain of corpses that reaches the heavens
木霊する　憎しみを
The hatred that echoes
lost lost lost! 消し去りたい
lost lost lost! I want to erase it
消し去りたい 掻き消す爆発音
I want to erase it, the drowning out explosion
Vielen Sperre Lost! Deckun Hilphe Halt!
Awake
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー
Dear Doppelganger
どうもこんにちは君の分身です
Hello, I'm your double
何の冗談か眼を擦ってみる
I rub my eyes, thinking it's some kind of joke
影が二つ伸びて　そしてまたまじわる
Two shadows stretch out and meet again
もう一人自分がいたならと願いました
I wished there were another me
そんな深層心理が僕を呼んだのさ
That deep psychology called out to me
それを望むのも　等しく全ての罪
Wishing for that is also equally a sin
過程如何で結果を欲しがる無意味無意味な代償
Wanting results regardless of the process,
a meaningless, meaningless price
ねぇこんな素晴らしいことがあるんだいいだろ
Hey, something this wonderful is happening, isn't it great?
ええやりますやります何でもやります 僕は君の分身です
Yes, I'll do it, I'll do anything. I'm your double
罪はライアー　メサイアは　You
The sin is a liar, the messiah is you
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー　君は誰　君は誰
Dear Doppelganger, who are you? Who are you?
あぁ混濁の末として　僕が誰
Ah, as a result of the confusion, who am I?
ねぇ　曝け出さない自意識証明の虚構なんてどこにもない
Hey, there's no such thing as a fiction of
unexposed self-conscious proof
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー　あれは誰　あれは君
Dear Doppelganger, who is that? That is you
蝕まれた存在に　世界は気付かれへん
The world won't notice your eroded existence
何もない　痛みもない
There's nothing, no pain
一石の人間が　狂った正解を染め上げてるん　パッパ
A single human is staining the crazy correct answer, pa-pa
どうも様子がおかしい　月曜日
Something seems wrong on Monday
一つずつ崩れゆく　辻褄が
The coherence is crumbling one by one
僕は誰にする？　お前は誰だと
Who should I be? Who are you?
ちょっと待って知らないその知りもしない言葉
Wait a minute, I don't know those words I've never heard
そうやっていつの間にやら影と溶けゆく
Just like that, before I know it, I'm melting into the shadow
僕はなんだろう　独存罪介して
What am I? Through the sin of sole existence
あいにく様あちらはあちらで随分心地よくて
Sorry to say, but that side over there is quite comfortable
もうあなたの居場所がここにないこと分かってるんでしょ
You already know there's no place for you here, right?
ねぇ　奪ったんだろ　バーバイだろう　今度はお前の番だ
Hey, you took it, didn't you? Bye-bye, now it's your turn
罪はライアー　イネヴァーは　You
The sin is a liar, the invader is you
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー　君は誰　君は誰
Dear Doppelganger, who are you? Who are you?
あぁ混濁の末として　僕が誰
Ah, as a result of the confusion, who am I?
増すはずの存在の命の椅子は一つだけ
There's only one seat for the life of an
existence that should increase
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー　あれは誰　あれは君
Dear Doppelganger, who is that? That is you
零れ出した一粒が　渇き果てるまで
Until the single drop that spilled out dries up
誰もいない　何でもいい
No one is here, anything is fine
普通を装う　狂った世界が染め上げてるん　パッパ
Pretending to be normal, the crazy world is staining, pa-pa
一人ずつ続き　響く五芒星の連鎖
Continuing one by one, the echo of the pentagram chain
僕のほうがちゃんと君を生きてやるから
I'll live your life better than you can
君も次の誰かちゃんと救わなくちゃ
So you have to make sure to save the next person too
もう分かってんだろ何をすればいいかさ
You already know what you have to do, right?
遠く誰か僕に奇跡をくれ
Someone far away, give me a miracle
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー　君は誰　君は誰
Dear Doppelganger, who are you? Who are you?
あぁ混濁の末として　僕が誰
Ah, as a result of the confusion, who am I?
もう止まらない物語　どうもこんにちは君の...
A story that won't stop anymore. Hello, I'm your...
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー　それは誰　それは僕
Dear Doppelganger, who is that? That is me
蝕まれた存在に　世界が気付こうとも
Even if the world notices the eroded existence
何もない　痛みもない
There's nothing, no pain
一石の人間が　狂った正解を染め上げるさ
A single human will stain the crazy correct answer
上手くやれよ　オレンパッパ
Do it well, oren-pa-pa
上手くやれよ ルンパッパ
Do it well, runpappa.
どうもこんにちは 君の分身です
Hello there. I am your alter ego.
Whoa! Thank you so much for watching
my #CHU2BAE Live today!
I can feel myself floating away...
...spiritually, psychologically, and physically.
But...
...it wouldn't be a live without a shill-taro!
I present to you the #CHU2BAE Merch Set!
Ta-da-da-da!
First up, we have an—I can't believe
the words are coming out of my mouth—
the official...
...JDONMY T-Shirt!
なんということですかこれは!?
What on earth is this!?
I can't believe it's come to this.
But yes, I've made the official 'Jdon' shirt for you all.
Um, the art was done by the ever-so-talented Dino.
Thank you so much for making
the Chunni shirt of my dreams!
It looks so cool! I'm in the pose.
You can wear this to all your Chunni outings,
or just every day at home, because every day is a Chunni day.
Please get the T-shirt! It is official.
I have a 'jdon my soul' t... I can't believe it.
Hi! Okay, next!
We have—da-da-da-da—we have the acrylic stand...
...of the wonderful 'Jdon' artwork that Dino has drawn.
So you can make your home even more Chunni.
This entire set is just making your entire life Chunni.
Isn't it amazing?
You can never have enough acrylic stands,
so please consider adding this to your collection. Yes, yes!
Okay, next!
Yes, there's still more! Now, to be initiated as a true Chunni,
you have to be carrying a secret medallion that no one knows about,
because it will give you secret powers of the Chunni.
So, I present to you a special medallion that has the powers of the Jdon...
...Jdon engraved into the front and back so that you never forget your Chunni soul
wherever you are. You have to carry this wherever you go
in order to be a true Chunni. Yes, yes, yes!
Okay, next!
Next we have the 'Cage of Ice' tray because Hakos Baelz
is forever trapped in a cage of ice,
and you can experience that too by making custom ice cubes of my face!
And also Los Squeakos, and also there's like cheese and other stuff.
But you know me, ice isn't enough,
so there's a possibility that it could withstand some heat,
maybe even some baked goods? I don't know.
Please check the product description before use, of course. But whoa!
The possibility is there. I don't know.
Anyway, next!
This time we also have a voice pack that narrates the life of a Chunni Rat.
It follows the journey of a Chunni princess who's been cast to the human world in hiding,
waiting to return while anticipating the attack of the century.
Believe it or not, this is based off an actual fanfic that I wrote by hand
that will never see the day of light... again.
The day of light? Did I just say that? The light of day again.
Thank you very much! Next!
Last but not least, we have the full set purchase bonus item, which is
the official 'Jdon' card that is signed by yours truly.
Honestly, I said I was never gonna do this again. But it was Chunni merch, I had to!
I will be signing every single card of every single person's full set purchase.
So please consider purchasing the full set, because I want all of you guys to be part of the Jdon club.
Thank you so much for the support as always, and I really hope you enjoyed this performance live.
I really, really pushed myself to the limit this time, so I hope it paid off.
Um, there's also the membership portion of this live, so it's not over yet!
It includes a very, very special performance.
So please join the Rat Pack if you haven't already. I'll see you guys there!
I am incapable of thinking anymore, so I'm-a just end it here.
Jdon my soul! Please get the merch! Whoa!
#CHU2BAE for life! Thank you!
CHU2BAEは命!
CHU2BAE is life!
"You can't be mad at me... I'm cute."
"The age of 30 is in demand"
"HAKOS BAELZ!"
"WITNESS ME!!!!!"
ご視聴ありがとうございました
Thank You for watching!!
Thank you for watching!!
I put everything into this live so I hope it was as CHUUNI as it could be ^ ^ SNEEEEAAAKEEER~!!
I hope it was a good show!!
ONWARDS TO THE NEXT!!